<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<!-- Cast-Allied Civ -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV_TADC2_ADJECTIVE">
			<Text>Cast-Allied</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV_TADC2_DESC">
			<Text>The Cast-Members Alliance</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV_TADC2_SHORT_DESC">
			<Text>The Lost Cast</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_TADC2_DOM">
			<Text>Good day to you, Pomni of The Amazing Digital Circus! You have escaped from your dimension of infinite imprisonment but have leapt from the frying pan into the fire. You find yourself in a different digital realm - created to simulate the ebb and flow of culture, technology, and war in humanity's past. You should not count on your opponents being peaceful, Pomni. Inexperienced leaders like you make for easy pickings.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Your friends from the Circus voted that you would act as leader, except for Jax. Following the vote, Jax decided it would be best to go off on his own. The remaining members offer help in the ways they know how. Ragatha works on an escape strategy. Gangle provides culture to your people. Kinger trains Acrobats to assist your military. And lastly, Zooble is the group's informant, gathering valuable intel.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]As dire as your situation is, try not to panic. Scared and unproven you may be, Pomni, but your fate is not sealed. You have friends, and as a team you all have promise. Are you up to the task of securing victory, and passing from this realm into the next? Will you build a civilization that stands the test of time?</Text>
		</Row>


		<!-- Cast-Allied Civlopedia (Civ) -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_TADC2_HEADING_1">
			<Text>About The Cast-Members Alliance</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_TADC2_TEXT_1">
			<Text>The Cast-Members Alliance is a group of 5 humans, trapped in a virtual world named The Amazing Digital Circus. Each of the Cast-Members offer a special talent to help this Civilization flourish. The five also take turns in naming newly-founded cities.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET] Pomni (Leader): Responsible for everything the others don't want to do.[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET] Gangle (Entertainer): Keeps the people happy the best she can.[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET] Kinger (Military Commander): Trains the Acrobats by throwing bananas in front of them constantly, until they learn to adapt.[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET] Ragatha (Strategist): Works consistently to encourage progress.[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET] Zooble (Secret Agent): Their detached limbs act as spies, harvesting vital intelligence from other Civilizations.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_TADC2_HEADING_2">
			<Text>How Did They Arrive Here?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_TADC2_TEXT_2">
			<Text>Recently, Gangle discovered a strange computer terminal on the Digital Circus grounds. After gathering the others, Gangle stood before it and was about to press a key right before Jax cracked his knuckles and bumped Gangle aside with his hips, sending her tumbling to the ground. "Hey Gangle, Mom said it was MY turn on the Xbox"[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]After clicking a few times, the terminal froze. Jax reared back his hand and punched the screen, shattering the thing to pieces and summoning a bright light. The group was teleported into The Void, the dangerous and infinite expanse surrounding their digital prison. All around them were icons from the terminal's screen. Caine would be here any moment to save them - but Pomni was determined to find out if she could do anything out in this Void to help their situation. "If there's any chance of getting out of here, I'm taking it!" she protests, reaching out to touch the closest icon. Pomni blinks out of existence, and the rest follow suit.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]They awaken in a green field, surrounded by dense fog on all sides. A chime rings out and a set of tutorial-like instructions appear before them. It takes the group some time to read these instructions, and the majority decide to elect Pomni as the leader of their 'Civilization'. Jax decides at this point to leave, believing he'd be better off alone.</Text>
		</Row>


		<!-- Cast-Allied Civlopedia (Leader) -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_TADC2_POMNI_HEADING_1">
			<Text>About Pomni</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_TADC2_POMNI_TEXT_1">
			<Text>An anxious and uncertain young woman, Pomni of the Amazing Digital Circus has accidentally arrived in the world of Civilization V while trying to escape from her afforementioned digital prison.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]With the intimidation skills of a puppy, Pomni is not a great fit among this world of well-seasoned, sometimes brutal leaders. Despite this, her friends are prepared to back her up. After all, they have very little options if they want to make it out of this mess alive...</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_TADC2_POMNI_LIVED">
			<Text>?? - ?? AD</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_TADC2_POMNI_NAME">
			<Text>Pomni</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_TADC2_POMNI_SUBTITLE">
			<Text>Jester of The Amazing Digital Circus</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEADER_TADC2_POMNI">
			<Text>Pomni</Text>
		</Row>


		<!-- Cast-Allied Unique Trait/Unit/Building -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_TRAIT_RAGATHAS_PLAN_SHORT">
			<Text>Ragatha's Plan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_TRAIT_RAGATHAS_PLAN">
			<Text>Cities (except the [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital) grant +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. This bonus triples once a city passes 5 [ICON_CITIZEN] Population. Receive a free Great Scientist upon completing your first social tree.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CASTALLIED_ACROBAT">
			<Text>Acrobat</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_CASTALLIED_ACROBAT">
			<Text>The Acrobat excels in agility, taking less ranged damage and able to move after attacking. The unit will also ignore terrain cost until upgraded into Pikemen. This unit is cheaper and as strong as the Spearman, which it replaces.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_CASTALLIED_ACROBAT_TEXT">
			<Text>In an effort to train their soldiers for anything, Kinger ditched the standard training regiment for a much tougher ordeal... Asking the recruits to run in a straight line while he throws a comical amount of bananas into their path. This rigorous program paid off, as the Acrobats exhibit superior movement compared to their Spearmen counterparts.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Unfortunately some of their Acrobat training becomes impractical once promoted to Pikemen in the Medieval Era. "Our equipment is too heavy now, they said. That's no excuse to slow down if you ask me!" Kinger complained aloud while shaking his head. "That's rich coming from the guy who can only move one square at a time" Zooble quipped in reply.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CASTALLIED_ACROBAT_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Acrobat is the Cast-Allied unique unit, replacing the Spearman. It possesses a permanent promotion that provides 16% extra defence from ranged sources and allows the unit to move after attacking. It also possesses a temporary promotion (until upgraded to Pikemen) that allows them to ignore terrain cost.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TADC2_GANGLES_THEATER">
			<Text>Gangle's Drama Theater</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TADC2_GANGLES_THEATER_ALT1">
			<Text>Gangle's Comedy Theater</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TADC2_GANGLES_THEATER_ALT2">
			<Text>Gangle's Tragedy Theater</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TADC2_GANGLES_THEATER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Upon being built, will provide an extra yield. Which yield is chosen is a 50/50 chance.[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Comedy Theater: +1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Tragedy Theater: +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture[NEWLINE]Requires no [ICON_GOLD] Gold maintenance.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TADC2_GANGLES_THEATER_STRATEGY_ALT1">
			<Text>Provides +1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness more than a standard Ampitheater. Requires no [ICON_GOLD] Gold maintenance.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TADC2_GANGLES_THEATER_STRATEGY_ALT2">
			<Text>Provides +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture more than a standard Ampitheater. Requires no [ICON_GOLD] Gold maintenance.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_TADC2_GANGLES_THEATER_TEXT">
			<Text>While building her theaters, Gangle considers the general vibe of the town. Some townsfolk are into her Comedy routines, while others prefer her Tragedy plays. Either way, she's excited about the opportunity to perform for so many people.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		
		<!-- Cast-Allied Unique Promotions -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_ACROBAT_TRAINING">
			<Text>Acrobat Training</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_ACROBAT_TRAINING_HELP">
			<Text>Acrobats may move after attacking, and have a 16% Ranged Defence bonus (equivalent to half of Cover I). This promotion is retained through upgrades.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PEDIA_PROMOTION_ACROBAT_TRAINING">
			<Text>Acrobat Training</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_ACROBAT_AGILITY">
			<Text>Acrobat Agility</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_ACROBAT_AGILITY_HELP">
			<Text>Acrobats ignore terrain cost while moving. This promotion is lost upon upgrading the unit to Pikeman.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PEDIA_PROMOTION_ACROBAT_AGILITY">
			<Text>Acrobat Agility</Text>
		</Row>


		<!-- Cast-Allied Cities (Naming Scheme: Cast takes turns picking city names) -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_NEW_HOME"> <!-- Pomni -->
			<Text>New Home</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_VAUDEVILLE"> <!-- Gangle -->
			<Text>Vaudeville</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_INPENETRABLE_FORTRESS"> <!-- Kinger -->
			<Text>Inpenetrable Fortress</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_TAILOR_TOWN"> <!-- Ragatha -->
			<Text>Tailor Town</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_WHATEVER"> <!-- Zooble -->
			<Text>Whatever</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_JESTERVILLE">
			<Text>Jesterville</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_RIBBON_RIVER">
			<Text>Ribbon River</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_ROOK_POINT">
			<Text>Rook Point</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_STITCHERY">
			<Text>Stitchery</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_I_DO_NOT_CARE">
			<Text>I Do Not Care</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_HARLEQUIN_HARBOR">
			<Text>Harlequin Harbor</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_CELEBRATION">
			<Text>Celebration</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_INSECT_COLLECTION">
			<Text>Insect Collection</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_BUTTONS_AND_THREAD">
			<Text>Buttons And Thread</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_GO_AWAY">
			<Text>Go Away</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_JAPE_JUNCTION">
			<Text>Jape Junction</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_MELODY">
			<Text>Melody</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_ROYAL_COURT">
			<Text>Royal Court</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_RAGDOLL_RANGE">
			<Text>Ragdoll Range</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_STOP_TALKING_TO_ME">
			<Text>Stop Talking To Me</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_SCHOOL_OF_JUGGLING">
			<Text>School Of Juggling</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_DRAMA_DOWNTOWN">
			<Text>Drama Downtown</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_SINGER">
			<Text>Singer</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_SUNNY_DAYS_AND_RAINBOWS">
			<Text>Sunny Days And Rainbows</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_THIS_IS_STUPID">
			<Text>This Is Stupid</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_XDDCC">
			<Text>XDDCC</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_ACOUSTIC_ALLEY">
			<Text>Acoustic Alley</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_BISHOPS_BLOCK">
			<Text>Bishops Block</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_YARN_CITY">
			<Text>Yarn City</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_HELP_ME_YOU_IDIOTS">
			<Text>Help Me You Idiots</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_BIG_TOP">
			<Text>Big Top</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_TIE_A_BOW">
			<Text>Tie A Bow</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_KINGSTOWN">
			<Text>Kingstown</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_NOT_LICORICE">
			<Text>Not Licorice</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_UH_YEAH_NO">
			<Text>Uh Yeah No</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_EXIT_DOOR_PLEASE"> <!-- Pomni -->
			<Text>Exit Door Please</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_ARTS_AND_CRAFTS"> <!-- Gangle -->
			<Text>Arts And Crafts</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_QUEENS_CHATEAU"> <!-- Kinger -->
			<Text>Queens Chateau</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_FABRIC_FIELD"> <!-- Ragatha -->
			<Text>Fabric Field</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_TADC_NO_MORE_NAMES"> <!-- Zooble -->
			<Text>No More Names</Text>
		</Row>
		
		
		<!-- Cast-Allied Spies -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_TADC2_0">
			<Text>Zooble's Leg</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_TADC2_1">
			<Text>Zooble's Arm</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_TADC2_2">
			<Text>Zooble's Hand</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_TADC2_3">
			<Text>Zooble's Shoe</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_TADC2_4">
			<Text>Zooble's Wing</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_TADC2_5">
			<Text>Zooble's Eye</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_TADC2_6">
			<Text>Zooble's Antennae</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_TADC2_7">
			<Text>Zooble's Claw</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_TADC2_8">
			<Text>Zooble's Shoulder</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_TADC2_9">
			<Text>Zooble's Body</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>